Helo, I am Federico, and that is what I have brought
in my bag for the torunament here,
in Asturias, the Open de España.
Starting with 3 putters, P2, P-Line,
soft edition, I would like to tell you that they are really soft,
they give you a lot of grip, and, of course,
for conditions like the ones we have today
that are a bit rainy, you have
a good grip, which is
really good.
A really good disc.
I buy them in pink because you can easily see them.
You throw them, you see them.
Also, I brought a first edition of a
P3X in S-Line.
This disc is stable.
It will come back.
You can throw this disc in any angle and
it will fight back to have fade.
Of course, if you throw it with a great deal of anhyzer.
It is not going to be enough, but well...
It is very reliable from tee pad, approaches
with side arm or backhand
and the good thing is that it can fight the wind.
In some ocations where there is a lot of wind
I would also use it for putting.
because it holds against the wind.
And the last putter I have is an Aviar
I believe that the plastic is KC-Pro, but I am not sure.
I bought it for 2€ a Manolo he got it also
for 2€ from.
our trainer in Germany. And he got it from the
former German champion.
That means, the putter flies right.
You don't need to be good.
The putter has history and he knows already
how to fly properly.
This is the disc that I use for every situation
where I don't know what to do.
it saves me many throws.
Now to the midranges..
I have four different molds right now..
Yes, correct.
Starting from understable to overstable:
first I carry a Matrix de MVP.
I bought this disc to... well, Manolo and I belong to the
Disc golf club Puerta de Doñana.
and I got it from our club.
And it has the stamp of our club.
The Matrix just flies straight..
You can throw it as hard as you want,
it will just fly straight.
The disc will hold the line.
Then I carry a Shark3.
The Shark3 is a fairly neutral disc.
It's a gift from Manolo for my birthday.
last year.
Very good disc, in plastic champion.
Then I have the MD4, in violet, also a
a gift from Manolo.
This keeps the line straight and even the
I can make it go a little to the right.
and he makes some very nice shots at me.
You can count on him with a headwind,
in any situation, it saves you from a mess.
You can also use it for forehand, it flies
straight ahead and come back.
And then the most stable disc, I think is the
more stable than I have in my bag
It is a Justice.
This doesn't even have a glide.
So my picture says here that it has glide.
1, that is, this doesn't fly.
You throw it away and it falls.
I have it in metal flake, also pink,
to find him.
I bought it from Ville in the pro-shop of the
discgolfpark of Málaga and this I use it on
all for forehand approaches, because
no matter what the situation, the weather,
whatever, you know you're throwing this away with all
your strenght and it's gonna come back.
This is gonna do the curve.
This isn't going away.
And the truth is, too, for some
curve with a skip that you have to do is
great.
Then I move on to the fairway drivers.
I have an FD2 that my friend painted for me.
Marcel.
Very cool disc, he painted it for me.
I use this mostly for forehand drives.
Also for backhand and for distant approaches,
when it's 60 or 70 meters, I already use this.
Then I have the Underworld.
This is the disc to make trick shots.
When I want to throw it like this, and the disc is
gets up and goes to the right.
I'm throwing it in forehand
so down and it goes up and holds
the whole line.
If I have to do a roller, this disc.
Very very very versatile.
And then we go to... I call it a fairway driver.
but they're on the line
Of velocity nine.
I've got two Getaways.
One of Danny Lindahl's stamp (Fuzion) and one of BioFuzion's.
The Getaway are discs that allow you to put
any line.
You put it in anhyzer and it's gonna keep the
anhyzer and he's gonna come back a little bit.
If he wants to do a roller, you can.
If you want to throw forehand, too.
It's a very versatile disc, fights the wind..
I recommend it.
Try it, if you can try it, give it a try.
Then I have a Thunderbird in Metal flake.
that my sister has given to me on
Christmas.
For forehands it has a mind-blowing flight.
Very very very straight and at the end it does have a little bit
of fade.
That's great. That's great.
It's really cool, too.
What have I got here?
Then we move on to something bigger.
I'm carrying the first disc I ever bought myself, personally,
his name is Tietäjä, I think I pronounce it
more or less well, but if not, some Finnish
will tell me it's wrong.
It's the Sorcerer.
In 170 grams.
This is tournament plastic.
Truth is, it's a little unstable, but
Not much. That means I can
throw it with a little hyzer and it's going to get
to the right, and it is gonna do a little bit of a curve
to the right and it's gonna come back.
And also, for forehand shots, you can
make a tunnel of 80 meters, straight straight straight
straight.
A great disc!
I've used it since day one and every time
I'm getting more fond of him.
Then we moved on to something more caliber, which
are two Destroyers.
Orange and blue.
I traded the blue one to Manolo for another disk.
The truth is, they're a little different,
the blue is very stable, the orange is more
neutral.
That's two Destroyers, with Star plastic.
That, I use for everything, right, left,
up, down...
A very good disc, I think anyone
who can have it in his bag would have it,
don't you?
I always buy them in different colors because
maybe it's silly, but when you want
to get out one from your bag you don't have to look at which one
is which one.
I know blue is the most stable,
I know that orange is more neutral and I
I just bought a red one that I hope will be
a little more understable, so always buying
by colors.
Then I have...
Whoo!
I forgot this one!
It's a PD2.
The truth is, it's not as stable as every PD2 I tried.
PD2s tend to go a lot to the left, but
this holds the line and then falls.
I use it to make skips, both, fore and backhand
and forehand anhyzer, to make an "S"
I don't throw it backhand much, but forehands
a lot.
And then I have two discs that I really like,
they are: The World.
It's a stable disk, it's almost like the PD2,
but the cool thing about this is that it's Elasto plastic.
Elasto is a plastic that is quite soft,
quite moldable and it is no longer produced
So if anyone wants to take this plastic,
run to the stores.
For cold conditions, conditions of
rain, and so
This type of plastic is highly recommended.
It doesn't get that firm.
And it has a good grip.
I think it's almost like Innova's G-Star.
And then the last one in my bag.
is a disc that was given in the "players package"
of the tournament in October in Mijas, which
is a queen, or, as it says here, "Emanta."
This disk is understable and has a lot
of glide.
It always comes back.
That's a very important thing to me.
I can throw it in forehand and with this I'll make you
100 meters with the whole curve.
And the truth is that it helps me a lot, because I
I don't have much strength and this disc
provides that versatility that I would want
to have.
And that's it, that's what I've brought here and
see you the next time!