Well, second day.
Plan for today: we're going to train,
to the same discgolf park again.
They already said when we started tomorrow, I
I start at 11:30AM and you start at...
At 10:38, I think, we start every 12 minutes,
which is really cool because that means
that we're not going to accumulate in any hole
in which the disks roll a lot, and that is
Something to appreciate, that's cool.
We're going to buy food for disc golf now.
i.e., water.
And I'll see you later.
We've finished training for tomorrow.
and we played pretty badly for what we wanted to have played.
The coolest thing about this field is that, you've got
that to control that when falling, the disk is not
Fuck it.
Well, and we're already leaving the park and
Now we're going to lunch.
And Manolo said, "Let's get some cider!
Yeah, man, yeah, since we're in Asturias.
You drink cider, man.
Cider for breakfast, cider for lunch,
cidra for dinner, cidra and inside the colacao..
Well, I'll see you at the cidrería!
Well, Manolo likes the cidrería so much.
who took one and bought one.
Are we gonna eat here, man?
First day of competition.
We have an impressive fog.
And good Fede. How motivated are you?
Motivated, a lot.
My throat hurts.
I'm fine. Let's see what comes out, I'll go.
positive, that is, I don't go with a "go" desto
to win" but...
What do you mean, no?
Man, I mean, you can fool yourself,
but..
Well, if you're fooling yourself enough
You may win!
You can fool yourself if you want to,
but there are people I've already seen with a rating
really high.
Well, we finished the round today.
We played... you say it.
Mehhhh
He has played "Mehhh" I wish I had
played that badly!
I mean, I've played even worse.
Nothing worked out, it was horrible today.
The baskets spit out my putts, three
or four times.
I hit every tree that exists.
A fucking piece of shit what I've done!
And you, Manolo, what's up?
This really pissed me off, man,
because I'm starting: Bogey, birdie, bogey, bogey...
and I was like...
What are you doing? What are you doing?
So,  we are going to eat, that it is already
the time.
Tomorrow we will surely play more
early.
The worse you play, the earlier you play.
I'm going to be the first to go...
Bye-bye!
We just got back from eating and drinking
a lot and it's 00:30 AM and
tomorrow we have to get up very early
because we've played really bad.
Well, at least Fede's been playing really bad.
and I've played bad, well, half bad.
I play...
I think Fede has to start playing
at 10:20 a.m. and I at 11 a.m..
is very ugly.
Conclusion: It is necessary to play better or to play in
Pro (Open), the Pro starts at 12 o'clock
in the morning..
It's true that it costs 20€ more to sign up
to Pro, but hey, what you're taking from it is:
"I don't have to sleep 7-5 hours, maybe 6.
hours..."
But what are you talking about, man, if it's the
00:30!
Come on, okay, I'm going to sleep 8 hours...
If we can get up at 8:30 a.m. and throw away
up and we still have time...
Well, let's go to sleep!
Good morning!
Second day of tournament, today we are going to have to
to overcome the 10-15-20 places...
At least...
That's my goal: 10 shots down!
What about you?
My thing is that yesterday I had 10 bogeys.
Not triple bogeys like Fede!
No, not me man, me all bogeys, bogey,
bogey, bogey..
And two birdies, but well...
With a 15-meter putt that's on "Television
Española"(TVE).
It's true, Manolo is on TVE!
"This is a sport for all ages
and cheap, the price of a record is around
12€.."
Well, after today's round I can already
to say goodbye to the tournament.
Completely.
So: See you later!
I played a +8 yesterday and I said, "I can...
to improve, I can improve."
I got a +20 today.
I took it on the 8th hole after shooting.
against the two trees, after I put myself
in O.B. twice and pass the mando,
I got a 10.
I mean, a +6 there.
PUM!
all over my face.
And three holes later I get a +4.
Suddenly a +10 and I am like "bye bye!".
From there..
It was a +20, that is..
I have to say one thing:
I started the round and said: "I am
tired."
We came here, just to get there: play.
The next day play and then start the
tournament, and I started the round today tired.
So So yeah..
Well, Manolo and I just got a cachopo...
It is a beast.
This is a disc next to the cachopo.
The cachopo is bigger than a disk.
I don't put it high because it's full
of shit.
Yes, please, I want to eat it.
Let's eat!
Good morning.
I played better yesterday.
The result has not been so good, because
I missed the putts, too low or too high.
I've improved nothing more than four shots and nothing,
we're coming.
Today is the worst day of all we've ever had.
you've had here.
If you can see there are clouds everywhere,
the field is wet, it rained at night,
there's wind, they've predicted rain during
the round..
Well, we're done playing the Open.
of Spain and after this I believe that
the best thing is going to be to go home because this
is depressing.
If yesterday I had the 10 and the 7, today I got
a nine...
I mean, roll down four times and say:
Dude, fuck it all!
I get as learning from this tournament:
Point number 1: You have to learn to shoot
measuring the angle where they're going to fall.
Point number 2:
Throw 300 meters at that angle.
Dude, wait a minute!
Point number 2: We have to improve our
physical condition.
I've played 5 days in a row disc golf.
On Saturday, yesterday, I was tired
I've taken shots today that I say: Dude, I could
to go much further, which I know, but
is that I'm busted.
Practice and knowing the park yes, but to play
Five days in a row, I don't think it's necessary.
At least from my point of view.
I played like shit.
That's it. That's it.
And there's nothing to say.
Let's practice.
And now that we're done playing.
we've finished everything and we're super blown up,
super tired and a little dissatisfied with
what we've done.
You know what we're gonna do?
Hole one of the "winter camp".
Let's go!
Manu has brought us here and we are going to play
one round and we're gonna give it all up right now.
We're going home now.
Yeah, let's go.
It's over now.
Yes, please, let's go home and sleep.
Me, too. I think it's a good idea to leave now.
so nothing. See you later!