Good morning!
We are going on a trip to Asturias
Passing through Madrid because there is no direct flight
We just got to the train station.
from Düsseldorf airport
And it's early in the morning, it's 5:25 in the morning.
I mean, we got up really early and
we left the house at 4:30.
I mean, we're super crazy
And that's it.
And now plane plane
BOOM! BOOM!
Well, this is a really cool thing that they have here.
at Düsseldorf airport
that the train that takes you to the terminal
It's a hanging train.
there's the railroad tracks, up there.
and downstairs then... it's floating.
And now we're gonna get on the floating train,
super cool!
And it seems to me that we're missing the train.
Let's go, the train's leaving! Ay ay
Ouch!
Yoo-hoo!
Let's go, let's go!
[music]
Hey, hey, hey!
Look how nice, how nice!
There, Victor likes this.
Victor approves
Press like
Victor gives it the go-ahead!
[music]
We're already in Madrid!
There's still one plane left to Oviedo.
and a couple of hours to a discgolf park.
which is the reason of the trip
[music]
Second plane, direction Oviedo
Here we go
[music]
We have just arrived in Asturias, we are collecting
our suitcases
And we've got everything
All the suitcases have arrived, which is a plus.
Here we go, aren't we?
Where are we going now?
Let's play
Let's eat!
Let's eat first.
Now let's eat. I'm hungry.
I want to play, and I like to play a lot.
I mean, I don't like not eating. I like to play,
but I also like to eat.
Let's go! Let's go!
So we've already reached the discgolf park and we're going
to throw a short round.
And thank you very much!
They've picked us up at the airport, they've...
Ana and Manu
Exactly.
They've taken us to eat in the middle of the mountain.
with breathtaking views,
perfect, luxurious, better can't be.
And now we're gonna play a little bit.
With a full belly!
[music]
well, well... Well! Well!
Look at this madness!
There's the basket!
What madness, what madness!
[music]
Byeeeeeee!
That's the game.
[music]
First impressions of...
I'm an idiot...
[music]
Ahhhhhhggg!
Oh, big skip!
Yeah!
[music]
That's the shot!
So, after we got up at 4:00 a.m.
get out at 4:30 in the morning, got in an
airplane at 7:40.
another at 11:50.
got here at 1:00, ate
played a round of at "Purification Tomas" discgolf park
which is super long, really tough
And we have taken a nap.
We've taken a nap... that was
friking great.
Let's eat it's time.
Yeah, and there we go to this street that's full of people.
people are all over the place!
there at the top. Look!
The cider boulevard
Here we go!
How's the cider Manolo?
It's good... it's good.
They're going to throw half a bottle on the ground, but good...