6 in the morning, today Manolo and I have the
first tournament of the German Tour, in Gillbach.
And I woke up early, and, because
my coffe machine is broken, I don't have any coffee.
I had to leave early in the morning,
Look how dark it is! To get coffee.
I really want to play and get rid of those bad
sensations of the tournament in Oviedo, so
I'll tell you more later.
Good morning! Well here we are in the small field
in Neuss Beckhofen. And it's a small field
of 9 holes and apparently we are going to play a
18 holes tournament, and what they've done is
to have 18 different exits for the 9 holes,
that is, each hole has 2 exits, let's say, and
there's like two fields. One that is field A
and another that is field B. Then each one
has 9 different holes. And that's it.
We're gonna warm up a little bit. It is already
time for it. I have had a 1:30 hour trip
in a car, which is a good thing..
And.. warm up. Let's go!
It's our turn to start and get onto this.
Let's rock it.
I haven't done a putt yet, but
Let's go, let's go.
As we are in carnivals, people
has come dressed to play, super cool. Look,
there's a dragon he's going to throw now.
Oy, oy oy oy...!
Uyyyyyy..
And here we have the Maja bee, which says
Hey! Hey!
We just finished the first round, two.
times the layout A. I've played a -2 and a -1.
and I found out half a minute ago that I've
taken four penalty points for
writing the wrong result on the paper. So now
I am on +1, when I had a -3 on the first round.
And how about you, Manolo?
Well, in the first round I played a -3,
which was the second best score of
the first round. I mean, me, super happy.
Super cool. The second round started and I said:
I know the course! Let's go!
I have to do this, boom boom... and I got a +3... that
is the second worst score of the second
round, I mean, I'm out of my mind. All in all
nothing, that's what you get for knowing the field. It is necessary
to play without knowing it. The course is not difficult,
the baskets all he's got is that they're
close to the OB or trees, like this one, that
is around things like for example
a piece of tree there with a lot of
twigs, that's good, because it makes the course
a bit harder, but it's got its little thing.
Let's see, the field, if you come and play to
make the shots that need to be made, you can
get out of here with a -6 of the 9 holes
you can do the -6 perfectly. And you stay
so relaxed, i.e.... This is no big deal.
Well, yes... They're calling us, we're leaving!
We're going to the second round, see you later!
We just finished round two and
I think it's been a little more difficult
than the first layout. I've played par. And you
Manolo?
In total I have played -1.
I liked the layout, I liked it more,
because he had more shots like 100-meter long to the
right, or things like that, it was beautiful.
I think the baskets could be a
a little farther away from things, because the
end was all: yes, 100 meters, I had
the distance, but if you don't give hit the right spot
then you get a shitty putt and
I didn't put them in. I mean, I haven't had
birdies for not being able to do the putts.
To me what I did not like of this field
is that they had here 9 holes with
their 9 exits, all right, and then they've taken
and they've said, well, we'll put some more
Nine exits, and that's how we make an 18-field, right?
The idea itself, perfect. Now, the implementation...
It has left a lot to be desired. Yes, in other words, you're going
from hole 5 to hole 6 and you cross through the
7, and you... Dude!....
And people waiting, I don't know... there's been like
two or three holes that have crossed the holes
and... no, no, not really. Let's see, no,
The thing is, we could have played a lot
better. This course you can play it perfectly
of the 9 holes, you could have played...
Minus two, minus three perfectly...
Minus two, minus three... and minus five too,
I mean, it's not like you say it's hard, but
I don't know...
But it has to be done.
So, let's see if the next time
we do and..
But it's been cool, we've played
a new course. It is true, a new course.
It's super far away from our house.
I'll never come here again in my life,
unless there's a tournament... but well...
See you next time! See you later!