Well, second day.
Plan for today: we're going to train,
to the same field again.
They already said when we started tomorrow, I
I start at 11:30AM and you start at...
At 10:38, I think, we leave every 12 minutes,
which is really cool because that means
that we're not going to accumulate in any hole
in which the disks roll a lot, and that is
He's very appreciative, he's cool.
We're going to buy consignments for the disc now.
golf, i.e., water.
And I'll see you later.
We've finished training for tomorrow.
and we played pretty badly for what we wanted to have played.
The coolest thing about this field is that, you've got
that to control that when falling, the disk is not
Fuck it.
Well, and we're already leaving the park and
Now we're going to lunch.
And Manolo said, "Let's get some cider!
Yeah, man, yeah, since we're in Asturias.
You drink cider, man.
Cider for breakfast, cider for lunch,
cidra for dinner, cidra and inside the colacao..
Well, I'll see you at the cidrería!
Well, Manolo likes the cidrería so much.
who took one and bought one.
Are we gonna eat here, man?
First day of competition.
We have an impressive fog.
And good Fede. How motivated are you?
Motivated, a lot.
My throat hurts.
I'm fine. Let's see what comes out, I'll go.
positive, that is, I don't go with a "go" desto
to win" but...
What do you mean, no?
Man, I mean, you can fool yourself,
but..
Well, if you're fooling yourself anyway.
You win!
You can fool yourself if you want to,
but there are people I've already seen with a rating.
of "and picomil."
Well, we finished the round today.
We played... you say it.
Mehhhh
He has played "Mehhh" I wish I had
played that badly!
I mean, I've played worse.
Nothing came out, it was horrible today.
The baskets spit out my putts, three.
or four times.
I've beaten every tree I've ever seen.
and for having.
A fucking piece of shit what I've done!
And you, Manolo, what's up?
He's really given me all the courage, man,
because I'm starting: Bogey, birdie, bogey, bogey...
and your uncle...
What are you doing? What are you doing?
That nothing, that we are going to eat, that it is already
the time.
Tomorrow we will surely play more
early.
The meaner you get, the earlier you play.
I'm going to be the first to go...
Bye-bye!
We just got back from eating and drinking
it's not written and it's 00:30 AM and
tomorrow we have to get up very early
because we've played a game of grief.
Well, at least Fede's been playing grief.
and I've played grief, well, half grief.
I played.
I think Fede has to start playing.
at 10:20 a.m. and I at 11 a.m..
is very ugly.
Conclusion: It is necessary to play better or to play in
Pro (Open), the Pro starts at 12 o'clock
in the morning.............................................................................................................................................................................................................................................
It's true that it costs 20€ more to sign up
to Pro, but listen, what you're taking to say:
"I don't have to sleep 7-5 hours, maybe 6.
hours..."
But what are you talking about, man, if it's the
00:30!
Come on, okay, I'm going to sleep 8 hours...
If we can get up at 8:30 a.m. and throw away
up and we still have